She can tell her best friend anything, except this one thing.
The Kissing Booth is a romance, comedy film directed by Vince Marcello.
When teenager Elle's first kiss leads to a forbidden romance with the hottest boy
in high school, she risks her relationship with her best friend.
Elle Evans, played by Joey King.
Lee Flynn, played by Joel Courtney.
Noah Flynn, played by Jacob Elordi.
Mrs. Flynn, played by Molly Ringwald.
Mike Evans, played by Stephen Jennings.
Brad Evans, played by Carson White.
The Kissing Booth is a 2018 American teen romantic comedy film written and directed by
Vince Marcello, based on the 2012 novel of the same name by Beth Reekles.
It stars Joey King, Jacob Elordi, and Joel Courtney.
The film follows Elle (King), a quirky, late blooming teenager whose budding romance with high school senior and bad
boy Noah (Elordi) puts her lifelong friendship with Noah's younger brother Lee (Courtney) in jeopardy.
The Kissing Booth was released on Netflix on May 11, 2018, and was dubbed a commercial success by the service, due
to it being widely viewed by subscribers, leading to the eventual production of a trilogy of films.
The film was largely panned by critics, who deemed its
storyline and themes to be clichéd.
A sequel, The Kissing Booth 2, was released on July 24, 2020, and the third
film, The Kissing Booth 3, was released on August 11, 2021.
The film explores themes of based on novel or book, crush, los angeles,
california, high school student, based on young adult novel.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.